萨姆纳警探在你那边怎么样
How's detective Sumner fitting into your unit?
我不是内务部的人
I'm not Internal Affairs.
如果被我发现猫腻
If I find out different...
你会后悔踏足21片区的
You'll wish you never set foot in the 21st.
这简直就是一坨狗屎...
This is complete horse--
你得身心投入进去  看着
Gotta get your hips into it-- like this.
一分钟就行
This'll only take a minute.
你找到下一个受害者了吗
You scope out your next victim yet?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你儿子有恋童癖  是个杀人凶手
Your son is a pedophile and a killer!
滚出去
Leave!
-杰  我是你的搭档  -怎么了
- Jay. I'm your partner. - Yeah.
-和我谈谈  -你不会想知道的
- Talk to me. - You don't wanna know.
霍斯特德  来我办公室
Halstead, my office.
我告诉过你罗迪杰的事要放手
I told you to let the Rodiger thing go.
我觉得朗尼会杀另一个孩子
I think Lonnie's gonna kill another kid.
有人在注意你  我只能告诉你这么多
You got eyes on you. I've warned you all I can.
哥们
Yo!
你们昨晚看比赛了吗
Did you guys catch the game last night?
最后18秒加时赛  凯恩得分反败为胜
18 seconds into overtime, Kane scores the backhander.
那家伙这个赛季跟打了鸡血一样
Guy's on fire this season.
-你们两个怎么了  -霍斯特德
- What's with you two? - Halstead.
局长
Commander.
霍斯特德  请坐
Halstead. Have a seat.
我站着就行
I'll stand.
昨晚下班后你去哪了
All right, after shift last night, where were you?
回家了  怎么了
Home. Why?
你是说
So you're telling us
昨晚你没出门吗
you didn't go out at all last night?
我昨晚看鹰队的比赛看到半夜
I'm telling you that I watched the Hawks game
然后就上床睡觉了
and I was in bed by midnight.
这是昨晚广景街跟西塞罗街处拍到的
This was taken last night near Broadview and Cicero.
这辆车是登记在朗尼·罗迪杰名下的
The car's registered to Lonnie Rodiger.
这是你
And that's you...
隔着两辆车
Two cars behind.
昨晚我回家时刚好开车跟在一个恋童癖后面
Okay, so I happened to be driving home behind a pedophile.
今早有人发现你说的这个恋童癖死了
Well, your alleged pedophile was found dead this morning,
在拉福莱特公园
Lafollette Park.
什么
What?
有人用绳子把他勒死了
Someone tied a cord around his neck.
所以你最好有更好的不在场证明
So I hope you have a better alibi
而不是什么看了一晚棒球比赛
than watching a hockey game...
还是一个人
alone.
查明真相之前
Until this is straightened out,
你正式停职
you're officially stripped.
内务部应该也会找你
So expect a call from Internal Affairs.
他们会尽快找你谈话的
They're going to want to interview you as soon as possible.
你是说审讯我
You mean an interrogation.
你知道规矩
You know how this works, son.
杰
Jay.
我一直想阻止那个变态
I'm the one who tried to stop that freak.
-现在却成了嫌疑犯  -我知道
- Now I'm the target. - I know.
拿着这个  这是丹·哈内斯的电话号码
Take this. It's the number for Dan Hanes.
他是我认识的最厉害的警察工会代表
He's the best police union rep there is.
记得打给他
You call him...
然后告诉我你想怎么处理这件事
and then you tell me how you want to handle this.
真是难以置信
This is unbelievable.
吉恩  我需要罗迪杰凶杀案的资料
Hey, Jin, I need the Rodiger homicide file.
作为案件嫌疑人  你这样做是违法的
As a suspect in his murder, that's highly unauthorized.
-拜托  老兄  -别再说了
- Come on, man! - We're done!
博伊特说如果我再帮你
Voight said if I help you one more time,
我就得回去分析街道和局部区域交通状况了
I'm back to manning traffic patterns for streets and SAN.
早就告诉过你让你小心
Told you to be careful, didn't I?
我刚被停职了
I just got suspended.
很惊讶吗
You're shocked?
别忘了是我把你带进情报组的
I'm the one who brought you into this unit.
托尼  不是我干的
Tony, this wasn't me.
我得去打卡上班了
I got to clock in.
马上给自己找个律师
Go get yourself a lawyer right now
先不要说废话了
and keep your mouth shut.
他  他突然就出现了  真的
He--he came out of nowhere, I swear.
-我没看到他  -我知道  女士
- I didn't see him. - I understand, ma'am,
但是我们得先离开
but we need you to get out of the way
这样消防员才能救人
so these men can do their jobs, okay?
老太太开车过十字路口
Old lady plows her boat through an intersection,
她是唯一一个毫发未伤的
and she's the only one without a scratch.
不要动
Hey, sit tight.
我们马上救你出来
We're going to get you out of there.
好了
Okay!
继续
More!
行了
Hold it!
不要动...
Hey, sit tight--
这辆车的司机打了我的人
Hey! the driver of this car, he decked my guy!
你个不知好歹的混蛋
You ungrateful prick!
-没事吧  -没事
- You all right? - Yeah.
事故责任又不在他  他跑什么
It wasn't his fault. Why'd he run?
看看车里的情况
Check the car.
能打开这个吗
Hey! what you got for this?
我去
Damn.
怪不得他跑得那么快
No wonder he was in such a hurry.
什么时候把车还给我
So when do I get my car back?
你的车是一起谋杀案的物证  所以
Well, it's evidence in a murder case, so...
可能会扣押一段时间
it could be impounded for a while.
我投保的保险不包括借用物品
Well, my insurance isn't going to cover a loaner.
芝加哥警署可以先给我一辆车用吗
Will the CPD provide me with one?
你尽管去停车场挑吧
You know what? Go ahead and pick one out from the lot.
去找前台的普拉特警长
Go talk to sergeant Platt, front desk.
她会给你钥匙的  好吗
She'll give you the keys, okay?
车主没前科
The owner of the car's clean.
两周前  车子在停车场
The car was reported stolen from a parking garage
被偷了
about a week ago.
后备箱发现的躯体上
Hey, the torso recovered from the trunk
有人工髋关节
had an artificial hip,
所以我让吉恩查编号
so I asked Jin to trace the serial number
查到与之配对的病人名字
and match it to the patient's name.
这样比基因检测来得快
Doing it that way's actually faster than a DNA test.
不用几周  我只要花几个小时就行了
Only takes me a couple hours instead of a couple weeks.
你回来是做正事而不是帮人干私活
It's a good thing you're back to doing your day job
真是一件好事
instead of personal favors.
继续查吧
Keep hitting the bushes.
你觉得是霍斯特德做的吗
Hey, so you think Halstead did it or what?
琳德赛  这是个问题而已
Lindsay, come on, it's a question.
知人知面不知心啊
You never know around here sometimes.
你什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
没什么
Nothing.
老实说  我一点都不同情他
To be honest, I don't feel any sympathy.
警方知道是谁干的吗
Do the police have any idea who did it?
我们还在努力查
We're still trying to piece that together.
盖尔  能给我加点奶吗
Gail, do you have any milk for this?
-好  -谢谢
- Oh, yeah. - Thank you.
-不好意思  -我不好意思
- Sorry. - I'm sorry.
他们把我停职了
They suspended me.
他们觉得是我干的
They think I did it.
如果是你做了什么
So if you did something...
现在跟我说
Then tell me now,
我们可以一起想办法
and we'll figure this out together.
杰  我这些年一直都想杀他
Jay, I have been fantasizing about it for years,
但我没有
but I didn't do it.
你为这个家做了这么多
After all you've done for this family,
如果你需要我去认罪
if you need me to confess...
我愿意去
I will.
他是被你害死的
Hey! he's dead because of you!
天哪
Oh, man.
如果你肯放过我们
None of this would have happened
这一切就不会发生
if you had just left us alone!
朗尼是咎由自取  你自己知道
Lonnie brought this on himself and you know it.
少了一个人啊
You're a man short.
霍斯特德因涉嫌谋杀正在接受调查
Halstead's under investigation for murder.
你想趁机进来吗
You want to cash in on that?
我有能力在情报组工作
I deserve to be in intelligence.
机会就是机会
An opportunity is an opportunity.
我从人工髋关节上找到线索了
I got a match on the artificial hip.
理查德·埃利奥特博士  DNA顾问
Dr. Richard Elliot... the DNA consultant
就是帮州检察官作证的那个
who testified for the state's attorney.
对  我知道他
Yeah, I knew him.
帮我们抓了几个重犯
Helped put away some major hitters.
昨天  他妻子提交了一份失踪人口报告
Well, his wife filed a missing persons report on him yesterday.
干得好
Nice work.
一起去看看
Let's take a ride.
两天前  他离开办公室后
He left his office two nights ago,
就没回家
and he never came home.
他在河滨路开车时还给我打过电话
He called me when he got on Lakeshore drive,
但之后就再没接过电话了
but then he never answered his phone after that.
作为控方的顾问
As a consultant for the prosecution,
我猜他受到死亡威胁了
I assume he's gotten death threats.
他为数百起和DNA有关的案子作过证
He's testified in hundreds of DNA cases.
我跟他说过  希望他退下来
I told him I wanted him to retire,
回去任教  但是他热爱他的工作
to go back to teaching, but he loved his work.
他是不是要为即将开庭的案子作证
Was he about to testify in any upcoming trials?
明天开审的案子
The trial was supposed to start tomorrow.
这个家伙
This clown,
尼古拉斯·德约洛维奇 又叫DJ尼克
Nicholas Djurovic, aka Nick the DJ.
法医概述
女士  你得和巡警进城
Ma'am, we're going to need you to go downtown
去...  处理遗体
with the patrolman to... deal with the remains.
遗体
"The remains," huh?
埃尔文  你开车过来接个人
Alvin, I want you to do a drive-by.
好  告诉我名字  我马上到
Yeah, just shoot me the name and I'll suit up.
话说霍斯特德到底怎么回事
So you'll let me know what's going on with Halstead?
我跟他说过  不要纠缠他的仇人
I told him not to pursue his vendetta.
他估计没听
Maybe he didn't listen.
那我们就不管他了吗
So we're just gonna to let this kid twist in the wind?
他自己惹的祸
He created this problem.
自己没办法解决的话
He can't figure his way out of it,
他就不配待在我们组
he doesn't belong in our unit anyways.
好
All right.
我认识一个警察
I know this one cop.
他身陷一起加重攻击罪的指控
He got jammed up on an aggravated assault charge--
如果需要你的建议  我自然会问
I want your opinion, I'll ask.
德约洛维奇  我们是CPD
Djurovic, this is CPD!
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD!
-安全  -安全
- Clear! - Clear!
你去哪里
Where you going?
你们不能这样...  突然闯进来...
Can't just... break in on me...
你想跑吗  尼克
You want to run, Nicky?
救我
Help me!
老兄  你怎么
You kind of find yourself
在这里玩性窒息啊
in an erotic asphyxiation situation here, bud.
你看不见吗
Can't you see? Just--
快...拉我上去  我要掉下去了
Try...get me...I might fall...
什么  我们要拉他上来吗
What, do we pull him up?
不  让他挂在那儿吧
Nah. Let him hang there.
有搜查令么...  你们
Got a warrant...
有主意了吗  埃尔
Do you have an idea, Al?
大概有了
I think I might.
尼克  你觉得呢
What do you think, Nicky?
-帮帮我  -什么
- Help me... - Huh?
你没权这样做
Oh, you got no right!
-放在他正下方  -对  就放那里
- Right underneath him. - Yeah, right there.
够高的
Pretty high up here.
放下来吧
Let 'er rip!
不管用啊
Well, that didn't work.
我要告你  我要告这座城市
I'm gonna sue you. I'm gonna sue the city.
我要告你妈生下你
I'm gonna sue your mother for having you.
我要告你爸想要...
I'm gonna sue your father for even thinking about doing--
闭嘴
Shut up.
你因为谋杀面临20年有期徒刑
You're facing 20 years for murder,
而这都要看埃利奥特博士的证词
and it all hinged on Dr. Elliot's testimony.
这听起来可像是肢解他的动机
Now, that sounds like motive to hack him up to me.
我听说那个博士死了会伤心吗
Am I shedding tears for that doctor?
不会
Nah.
但如果我不打算真的"告别"的话
But do you think I'd be throwing a going-away party
你觉得我会开一个告别派对吗
if I wasn't actually... going away?
所以这次你的确犯了谋杀罪喽
So you're saying you're guilty of the murder they got you on?
必须承认  现在那个博士死了
Got to admit, now that the doc's dead,
我突然觉得自己无罪了
I'm suddenly feeling not guilty.
如果你没有杀埃利奥特
If you didn't kill Elliot,
你就是伊利诺斯州犯罪史上最幸运的被告
you're the luckiest defendant in Illinois criminal history.
认出来了吗
Recognize him?
这不是逃跑的那个人
It's not the guy who ran.
你确定吗
You sure?
确定
Yeah, positive.
躯干主人的死亡时间
Well, time of death on the torso
被确定为48小时前
was determined to be 48 hours ago,
德约洛维奇那时在密尔沃基市的
Same time Djurovic was visiting his mother
一家疗养院看他母亲
in a nursing home in Milwaukee.
他们有他的签名和监控影像
They've got him signed in and on camera.
可能他雇别人干的
Maybe he farmed out the hit.
不  不应该
No, it doesn't make sense.
他才是会被雇来杀人的杀手
He's the one criminals farm this sort of thing out to.
你介意去看几张脸部照片吗
You mind coming to take a look at a couple mug shots?
当然可以
Sure.
很高兴再见到你
Good to see you again.
我也是
You, too.
我希望是在更好的情况下见面
I wish it was under better circumstances.
你妹妹怎么样了
How's your sister?
她好多了  谢谢
She's doing better. Thanks.
近期释放的埃利奥特博士作证过的罪犯
Recently paroled ex-cons Dr. Elliot testified against.
你认出谁了吗
You recognize anybody?
托尼·强斯顿  案件号  54885312
这个家伙
That guy.
这就是我们从车里救出的家伙
That's the guy that we pulled out of the car.
托尼·强斯顿  北佬帮的成员
Tony Johnston, a member of the Northsiders.
看来你们认识他
I take it you know him?
他们是源自斯泰特维尔监狱的
They're a hardcore white supremacist gang
一个白人至上主义黑帮
that formed in Stateville Prison.
对
Yeah.
强斯顿因为多起强奸案被判刑
Johnston did time for multiple rapes,
两周前获保释等候上诉
was released on appeal two weeks ago,
在西湖街上有一家修理厂
owns a salvage yard over on West Lake.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
安东尼奥  拿大家伙
Antonio, get the gauge.
拿来了
Got it.
不管用
That didn't work.
上面有门栓
It's got a gate bolt.
来看这里
Hey, come here.
小心点  那是盐酸
Hey, careful. That's hydrochloric acid.
什么  天呐
Hmm? Oh!
强斯顿不是不小心滑进桶里去的
So Johnston didn't accidentally slip into that tub.
法医在他的脖子上发现了勒痕
M.E. found strangulation marks on his neck,
或者说是在脖子剩下的部分上
or what was left of it.
他的电话上有什么线索
What about his phone?
过去24小时内给他的律师
Two dozen calls to his lawyer
打了二十几个电话
in the last 24 hours.
她肯定知道些什么
She's got to know something.
好  带上萨姆纳去见强斯顿的辩护律师
All right, take Sumner, go see Johnston's mouthpiece.
看看能查出什么
See what you can dig up.
不  等等
No, wait. Hold on.
安东尼奥  你跟她去
Antonio, you go with her.
为什么不能是我和萨姆纳
What's wrong with me and Sumner?
说啊
Say it.
我觉得男女搭配比较好
I think it's better if partners are male-female.
-我们走  -艾琳
- Let's go. - Erin.
滚蛋
Kiss my ass.
你的律师与当事人保密特权已经结束了
Your attorney-client privileges are over.
我们在一个强酸桶里找到了托尼·强斯顿
We found Tony Johnston in an acid bath.
他为什么希望埃利奥特博士死
Why would he want Dr. Elliot dead?
他觉得埃利奥特弄错DNA证据
Well, he believed Elliot misread the DNA evidence
来支持起诉
in favor of the prosecution.
他认为  他因为没有犯的罪行
In his mind, he spent seven years inside
被关了七年
for a crime he didn't commit.
-你怎么认为  -我负责托尼的上诉
- What do you think? - I led Tony's appeal
还让他被提前释放
and got him an early release from prison.
所以很显然埃利奥特博士的研究有所疏漏
So obviously, Dr. Elliot's research had some holes in it.
你和你的客户好像走得很近
Sounds like you get pretty close to your clients.
我相信公平正义
I believe in justice being done.
你花费数年帮人战胜陈腐的系统
You spend years helping people get through a corrupt system,
就自然会关心这对他们生活的影响
you begin caring how it affects their lives.
他24小时内给你打了二十几个电话
He called you two dozen times in 24 hours.
什么事情这么重要
What was so important?
托尼担心他的性命
Tony feared for his life.
他在害怕谁
Who was he so afraid of?
一个叫雅各布·西姆斯的人
A man by the name of Jacob Sims.
他是北佬帮的首领
He's the head of the Northsiders.
托尼在监狱里的时候
While Tony was in prison,
西姆斯接管了他的修理厂
Sims took over his salvage yard
在那里做黑车交易
and used it to traffic in stolen cars.
托尼出狱后  他俩因为交易的事起过争执
After his release, the two had a falling out over business.
那强斯顿为什么觉得你能保护他
And what did Johnston think you could do to protect him?
我不过是给过他一些法律建议
I was merely offering legal advice.
为非法交易提供法律建议吗
Legal advice for an illegal business?
拜托  搞笑呢
Come on, humor me.
和西姆斯这样的人做事
Working with a man like Sims--
能早跑还是趁早跑吧
You cut your losses and you run.
跟踪罗迪杰一家
Stalking the Rodigers,
他们已经多次投诉过你
the multiple complaints on record against you--
警察栽在比这还小的事上我都见过
I've seen cops flushed down the toilet for less than this.
告辞了
I'm going to go now.
希望你聪明点儿
I'd hoped that you'd be smarter.
向内务部提交一份正式说明
Give IAD a formal statement,
我们明天就不用费那个事开听证会了
and we can all avoid a very messy hearing tomorrow.
你所有的证据只有我开车的一些照片
All you have on me is a few pictures of me driving.
你觉得是霍斯特德干的吗
Halstead. Do you think he did it?
就算我知道  你觉得我会告诉你吗
If I knew, you think I'd tell you?
好吧
Okay.
我之所以叫你过来是想说
Second reason I called you in here,
你该好好看着他
you should have kept better eyes on him.
你觉得这是我的错
You're saying this is my fault?
他是你的人  是你带进来的
He's your guy. You brought him in.
你做了那么多错事  现在反而来指责我吗
You're judging me, after everything you've done?
内务部刚把手铐从你手上解开没多久
IAD put you in cuffs a week ago.
是啊  反正那事我已经搞定了
Yeah, cuffs I got out of.
但是一开始我就告诉你  你想带他进来
I told you, day one, you want to bring this kid in our unit,
可以
fine.
但你要为他的行为负责
But I hold you responsible for his actions.
这条仍然有效  安东尼奥
That hasn't changed, Antonio.
什么事
Yeah?
北佬帮的黑车交易场
Northsiders' chop shop.
我弄了一份与被发现黑车有关的
I made a list of all the license plates
车牌号清单
connected to the cars we found,
为以防万一  我提个醒
Put an alert out, just in case.
半小时前  罗斯蒙特警方
Half an hour ago, Rosemont police spotted a Mustang
在会议中心的停车场
with one of the stolen plates
看到一辆挂着失窃车牌的野马汽车
in the parking lot of the convention center.
枪支展销会
这里是罗斯蒙特警署  已就位  准备进入
Rosemont PD, in position and ready to move in.
罗斯蒙特警署  解除戒备状态
Rosemont PD, stand down, stand down.
我们要先确定嫌疑人
We will wait for the suspect to be identified.
盯好每个出口还有外卖出入
I want all these exits covered and set up for takeaways.
注意车辆
Maintain eyes on the vehicle.
这应该就是世界上抓捕嫌疑人
Talk about the worst place in the world
难度最高的地点了吧
to take down a suspect, right?
奥林斯基  你看到西姆斯了吗
Olinsky, you I.D. Sims?
看到了  他正要出去
Yeah, on his way out,
还带着一把崭新的AKM突击步枪
and he's got a brand-new shiny AKM.
好的  在西姆斯把抢放进车里之前
All right, nobody pops off until Sims gets the artillery
谁都不要行动  他正朝这个停车场走
into his vehicle, he's out of this parking lot.
我们一会儿把他困住
We'll just box him in.
巡逻队  去前面
Patrol, position to the front.
收到  马上
10-4, moving in.
嫌疑人没有武器了  开始行动
Suspect unarmed. Moving in.
-他提前行动了  -罗斯蒙特警署  后退
- He's jumping the gun. - Rosemont PD, pull back!
后退  罗斯蒙特
Pull back, Rosemont!
不许动  警察
Stop! Police!
大家都看准目标
Everybody, watch your aim!
这里普通民众太多
We got civilians all over!
警察  放下枪
Police! Guns down.
他去哪了
Where is he?
所有人  散开搜索
Everybody, spread out!
找到他
Find this guy!
大家都别乱跑
Everybody stay where you are!
-不要惊慌  -去那边
- Calm down! - Go that way.
中弹的那个罗斯蒙特警官
The Rosemont police officer who was shot
在去医院的路上死亡
died on the way truck to the hospital.
留下了妻子和两个孩子
Wife, two kids.
我们失去他了
We lost that guy.
所以只要能找到那混蛋  刀山火海我们都要去
So we go down whatever dark hole we have to to find him.
还好吧
You doing all right?
-还好  -真的
- Yep. - Yeah?
这是你第一次开枪吗
Is this your first time firing your weapon?
是啊
Yeah.
好  等你写完
All right, well, when you finish up,
我们出去走走吧
let's get out of here, yeah?
谢谢你还来见我
I appreciate you meeting me.
-你搞什么  -是你干的吗
- What the hell? - Did you do it?
我已经告诉过你...
I already told you--
-是不是你干的  -不是
- Did you do it? - No!
如果我要杀朗尼·罗迪杰
If I was going to kill Lonnie Rodiger,
他奸杀本·科森的那晚
I would have done it the night he raped
我就动手了
and he killed Ben Corson.
我差一点就杀了他
And I was this close!
朗尼·罗德杰的案件文件
Lonnie Rodiger's homicide file.
不要跟别人说是谁给你的
No one knows where you got that.
托尼·强斯顿提到过雅各布·西姆斯吗
Did Tony Johnston mention anything about Jacob Sims?
我不记得
Nothing specific I can recall.
没有什么秘密地点吗  常去的地方什么的
No stash house or, you know, hangout?
我们可能不知道的藏身之处
Someplace off the radar we might find him?
你要理解  我之前只是强斯顿的律师
You have to understand I was merely Johnston's lawyer.
除了他的案子我们不会讨论别的
We didn't discuss much else other than his case.
爸爸让我来和你说  晚餐已经好了
Dad wanted me to tell you dinner's ready.
好  你们先吃吧  我马上来
Okay, you two start eating. I'll be right in.
没出什么事吧
Is everything okay?
没事  亲爱的  只是工作
Yeah, it's fine, honey. It's just work.
去吧
Okay.
不用我跟你说你都知道西姆斯是个疯子
Look, I don't have to tell you, Sims is unhinged.
他可以根据事实进行推理
He could put two and two together,
然后以为  你说了什么
figure out that... you said something.
他有可能会在这里出现
There's a possibility he might show up here.
我不知道
I don't know.
也许我是希望成为一个
Maybe I was hoping I'd be one of those cops
在整个职业生涯中一枪不开的警察
that go their whole careers without firing a single shot.
你想升职  对吗
Well, you want to be upstairs, right?
当然
Yeah, of course.
那我觉得你开枪是件好事
Well, then I think it's good you popped your cherry now,
因为我可以保证  这肯定不会是你最后一次
because I promise you, this is not going to be the last time
拔枪射击
you fire your weapon.
那你呢  你的秘诀是什么
What about you? What's your trick?
我没有认真想过
I don't really think about it.
所以你只是把自己的感受隐藏起来
Oh, so you just bury your feelings,
像其他男人那样吗
like a typical guy.
不  不是有意为之
No, it's not intentional or anything.
我只是不怎么受影响
I just, really, it doesn't bother me.
你从来不想被你杀掉的嫌疑犯吗
You don't ever think about the suspect you killed?
我叔叔曾经跟我说过两个和尚的故事
My uncle used to tell me this story about two monks...
好吧
Okay.
他们在河边发现一个任性的少女
who find a wayward maiden on the riverbank, right?
一个和尚对另一个和尚说
And one monk says to the other monk...
-这是年轻一点的那个和尚  -好吧
- This is the younger monk. - Okay.
这是在他们过河之后
This is after they cross the river.
要点在于  不要总把问题挂在心上
The upshot is don't carry your problems around with you.
和尚
Monks?
Monks.
谢谢  谢谢你的啤酒
Thanks for the-- thanks for the beer.
不客气
Yeah.
你想找人聊天的话我随时奉陪
I'm around anytime you need to talk.
-好吗  -好
- All right? - Yeah.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不  我
No, I'm--
别这样  没事
No, hey, it's okay.
我觉得你可能在喝酒
I figured you might be drinking.
男人不应该自己喝闷酒
A man shouldn't be drinking alone.
怎么  你是在拖车公园长大的吗
What, were you raised in a trailer park?
效果都一样  对吧
Works the same, right?
没错
Yeah.
以前我的枪和警徽也被收走过
You know, I had my piece and badge taken away from me.
世界上最痛苦的事莫过于此
It's the worst feeling in the world.
是因为布朗宁的事吗
Was it the Browning thing?
没人以为我们会把他活着送到目的地
No one expected us to deliver him alive,
所以
so...
我们决定干脆直接不送了
We just decided not to deliver him at all.
是博伊特让你这么做的吗
Did Voight make you do it?
那晚没有人让任何人做任何事
No one made anyone do anything that night.
我没有杀朗尼
I didn't kill Lonnie.
别紧张
It's no sweat.
我能让你看点东西吗
Can I run something by you?
当然可以
Yeah, yeah.
菲尔·罗迪杰做出了声明
So Phil Rodiger gives his statement,
他说
and he says...
他儿子那晚没有回家
that his son never came home that night.
但我知道他回了
But I know he did.
我的手榴弹去哪儿了
Where the hell is my grenade?
你的什么
Your what?
是个镇纸
Oh, it's a paperweight.
我大学毕业时别人送给我的礼物
A gift that I got when I graduated the academy.
如果不在这里的话...
If it's not nailed down around here...
普拉特正在给
Hey, Platt's taking donations
罗斯蒙特那个被杀害的警察募捐
for the Rosemont cop that was killed.
多掏点
Dig deep.
非常感谢
Much appreciated.
伯吉斯最好别哭穷
Burgess better not cry poor.
我不管博伊特或是别人怎么看你
Hey, I don't care what Voight or anyone else thinks about you.
只要你对得起自己坐的位置
As long as you honor that chair you're sitting in,
我就支持你
you'll be right by me.
看来我不是这里唯一一个没有社交生活的人
I see I'm not the only one without a social life here.
调查员搜查了修理厂的犯罪现场
So investigators searching the crime scene at the salvage yard
发现了几百克病毒
found a couple hundred grams of meth,
一箱武器  还有这个
a cache of weapons, and this.
你之前询问的那个律师
That lawyer you interviewed earlier--
我觉得你应该让她来一趟了
I think you're going to want to bring her in.
关掉
Turn it off.
求你了
Please.
我猜摄影师不是你的丈夫吧
I'm assuming the cameraman isn't your husband.
当然不是
Of course not.
那是谁
Then who is it?
想让我把你丈夫带来看看吗
Want me to bring your husband down here to watch?
托尼·强斯顿
Tony Johnston.
我是被迫的
I was forced into it.
我怎么觉得你挺享受的
Looks like you were enjoying it to me.
我遇到雅各布·西姆斯的时候正在帮强斯顿上诉
I was working on Johnston's appeal when I met Jacob Sims.
我需要他的证词
I needed his testimony for the case.
他从去年开始跟踪我
Over the last year, he began stalking me.
为什么你不找警察
Why didn't you reach out to the police?
你也知道他们的名声
You know their reputation.
他威胁我
He threatened me.
他说如果我不从  他就要伤害我的家人
He said if I didn't, he'd charge a family tax.
要是我不跟他发生性关系
Either I have sex with him,
他就杀了我丈夫和女儿
or he kills my husband and my daughter.
他说他会把那段录像寄给所有我认识的人
He said he'd send that video to everyone I know.
你怎么看
So what do you think?
或许强斯顿和西姆斯为了她闹翻了
Maybe Johnston and Sims had a falling out over her?
那也不能解释他们为什么杀埃利奥特博士
That doesn't explain why they hacked up Dr. Elliot.
我有个线人  他过去是北佬帮那边的
I have a CI who used to be a Northsider.
或许他知道西姆斯的事
Maybe he knows something about Sims.
你还跟白人至上主义者有来往
You're tight with a white supremacist?
不过是逢场作戏
Like this.
-能不能...  -当然
- Can you... - Yeah, of course.
谢谢
Thanks.
我不是那种破坏别人家庭的人
I'm not a home wrecker.
什么  你说笑吗
What, are you kidding me?
你算是这里最正直的警察了
You're like the most honest cop in this building.
所以我们就当什么都没发生过吧
Then we can agree what happened never happened.
伯吉斯  听着
Hey, Burgess, look.
求你了
Please.
我们继续当朋友吧
Let's keep it as friends.
记忆已消除  行了吧
Erased from my memory. All right?
鲁塞克刚跟我说我占了两个车位
Ruzek was just letting me know that I was double-parked,
我现在出去挪一挪
so I'm going to go move it.
对了  我就在找这个呢
Oh, right, yeah. I've been looking for that.
我看看我有多少
Let me see, um... let me see how much I have.
太好了  给
Oh, great. There you go.
在之前给警方的口供里
In the statement you gave the detectives,
你说你晚上十点之后就没见过朗尼了
you said that you didn't see Lonnie after 10:00 P.M.,
你说他开车走了就没再回家
that he went for a drive and he never came back.
我那晚跟踪了朗尼
I was following Lonnie that night,
这段监控被拍到后不久
and not long after these pictures were taken
我就看着他走进了家门
I watched him walk into your house.
朗尼找猎物找累了  于是就回家了
Lonnie got tired of hunting, so he went home.
而他的死亡时间
And according to the time of death,
是在我拍下这张照片后一小时
he was killed an hour after I took this photo.
你儿子不是在拉福莱特公园被杀的吧
Your son wasn't killed in Lafollette Park, was he?
我不知道你在胡说什么
You got no idea what you're talking about.
菲尔  你去哪儿
Phil, where you going?
是你杀了他
You killed him.
他是个变态
He was sick!
这么多年来  我却一直在维护他
All those years, I defended him.
还在吸小号手[香烟]啊
Still smoking those Buglers?
我跟你的假释官聊过了
I checked with your parole officer.
据说你可是个模范公民
Supposedly you're a model citizen,
就是上个月酒后驾车了
except for that DUI you got last month.
熊队输了  我就有点喝多了
Bears lost. I went a little overboard.
芝加哥的橄榄球队
你找我有什么事
So what do you need?
我知道你几年前退出北佬帮了
I know you left the Northsiders years ago,
但我想知道他们老大雅各布·西姆斯的事
but I need the lowdown on their shot caller Jacob Sims.
我看到新闻上说了  他杀了个警察
I saw it on the news. Killed a cop.
换了是我  我肯定不会留在这等死
That was me, I wouldn't stick around.
是啊  所以我们在机场  公路
Yeah, we got alerts out at O'hare, midway,
车站和工厂都设了警戒
Union Station, the works.
我想你应该知道
Figured you'd know
北佬帮有没有什么秘密交通方式
if the northsiders had an underground railroad.
知道金盆洗手有什么坏处的吗
You know what the problem is with being legit?
我得真真实实付账单
I actually got to pay the bills.
这家伙有悬赏金
There's a reward for this guy.
只要你给我点有用的料
You give me something that checks out,
我会让你拿到钱的
I'll make sure you get it.
北佬帮是芝加哥唯一一个
Northsiders are the only crew in Chicago
制造冰毒却没被抓住的团伙
that get away with making meth.
他们每天都有伪装过的货船
They use a big rig with false walls
从芝加哥开往印第安纳波利
that leaves every day from Chicago to Indianapolis.
知道货船公司的名字吗
You got a name for this trucking company?
不知道  他们每隔几个月就换一家
Naw. They changed it every few months.
不过我记得他们租用过南拉辛的货运场
But I do remember they used a trucking yard on south Racine.
先给你这么多
A little something for now.
是哪辆
Which one?
那就得我们自己查了
That's what we have to figure out.
如果西姆斯真在其中
If Sims is in one of them,
用这个就能探测到他的体温
we'll catch his body heat on this.
好了  你留在这  等有需要你再进去
All right, hang back until we need you.
下一辆去印第安纳波利的船是什么时候
When's the next rig to Indianapolis?
有三辆  在三  十二和十六号码头
There's three of them-- dock 3, 12, and 16.
安东尼奥  去查十二和十六号码头
Antonio, scan docks 12 and 16.
我们查三号
We got number 3.
你去办公室等着吧  先生
Why don't you go wait in the office, sir?
我要看到图像
I need an image.
芝加哥警察  雅各布·西姆斯
Chicago PD, Jacob Sims!
放下武器
Drop it!
我来照顾他  快去
I got him! Go!
亚当
Adam.
-来  让我看看  -我中枪了
- Come on, let me see. - I got hit.
好了  没事  被防弹衣挡住了
All right, all right, the vest stopped it.
你没事  没事
You're okay. You're okay.
深呼吸  没事了
Take a deep breath. You're all right.
趴下
Stay down.
Stay down!
趴下
你的情报很准确
That was good intel.
这次的报告就由你来写
You can write the report on this one.
去拷上他吧
Cuff him.
报告上要写
Should I include the part
你向手无寸铁的疑犯开枪的事吗
where you shot an unarmed suspect?
这个就不用写了
No, you can leave that part out.
雅各布·西姆斯
So Jacob Sims...
他招了些很有意思的事
he had some interesting things to say.
真高兴你们终于抓住那个禽兽了
I'm just happy that you finally caught that animal.
这是州检察官寄来的你的案宗
We got your case files sent over from the states attorney.
埃利奥特博士就是你之前
Dr. Elliot was the reason
十个案子输掉了八个的原因
you lost eight of your last ten cases,
而且你下个月又得和他在法庭上见面了
and you were set to face him in court next month.
我下个月有很多案子
I have multiple cases next month.
我们还跟你的同事谈过了
We also spoke with your law partners.
他们说根据你最近的输赢记录来看
They said with your record of wins versus losses lately,
你就快就会被投票从律师事务所除名了
you're close to being voted out of the firm.
我觉得埃利奥特会让你失去合伙人资格
I think Elliot was about to cost you your partnership,
你在律师事务所里的股份
your stake in the firm,
还有林肯公园里价值百万的连栋别墅
million-dollar townhouse in Lincoln Park.
你是在暗示我杀了埃利奥特博士吗
Are you insinuating that I killed Dr. Elliot?
不是
No.
你做的那个小性爱录像带
That little sex tape you made?
我认为是你勾引西姆斯和强斯顿
I'm thinking you seduced Sims and Johnston
对你那样做
into doing it for you.
一个没处理好埃利奥特博士的尸体...
One screws up disposing the body...
所以另一个就杀人灭口了
The other kills him so he can't talk.
然后你怂恿我们去逮捕西姆斯
Then you sic us on Sims
来帮你收拾烂摊子
to clean up your mess.
我是受害者
I am a victim.
你们是相信一个既种族歧视又反社会
Are you going to believe the accusations of a racist,
又有犯罪前科的人的话  还是我的话
sociopathic ex-con, or me?
问我吗  我会相信前者
Personally? The first one.
那就拿出证据
Prove it.
-我们只能把她放了吗  -那能怎么办
- We're just going to kick her? - What do we got?
我们有她和另外两名嫌疑人合流的证据
Evidence of her with those two suspects.
什么  两个有犯罪前科的人和一盘性爱录像带
What, two ex-cons and a sex tape?
不行  放她走吧
No, kick her.
向州检察官提出诉讼
File it with the states attorney,
看看事情有何发展吧
see how far it goes.
听说他们把菲尔·罗迪杰逮捕了
Heard they brought in Phil Rodiger.
我一直不愿相信
I never wanted to believe
我儿子能做出那种事
my son was capable of such a thing.
我在他的电脑上发现了一些照片
I found some pictures on his computer--
男孩子
Boys...
都是跟科森一样大的男孩子
The same age as the Corson kid.
我找他对质
I confronted him.
你是怎么杀死朗尼的
How did you kill Lonnie?
我们争吵起来
We fought.
我拿起一根腰带
I picked up a belt...
一直勒着他
And I kept choking him.
然后你在公园里抛了尸
And then you dropped his body in the park.
很高兴你回来了
Hey, good to have you back.
这些是你的
These are yours.
我们一起出去喝一杯吧
We all going for a drink?
不了  我要去别的地方
No, I got someplace I got to be.
我从未怀疑过你  兄弟
I never doubted you for a second, bro.
你和那个"叛逆儿童"是怎么回事
What's up with you and Rebel without a cause?
鲁塞克吗
Ruzek?
没什么啊  他都订婚了
Nothing. He's engaged.
我当警察已经很多年了  伯吉斯
I have been a cop a long time, Burgess.
我懂肢体语言
I know body language,
你的肢体语言意思是你被上了
and yours said you got felt up.
警长  不可能
Sergeant, no way.
-你几岁了  -26岁
- How old are you? - I'm 26.
这么跟你说吧  伯吉斯
I'll tell you what, Burgess.
什么
What?
趁年轻的时候好好玩玩吧
Why don't you have fun while you're young?
其实这么多年
God knows I've tasted my share
我在警局内部已经尝过禁果了
of forbidden district house fruit over the years.
埃尔  你在结婚之前临阵退缩过吗
Hey, Al, you ever get cold feet before you got married?
改主意了吗  孩子
Getting second thoughts there, kid?
不是  或许吧
No. I mean, maybe, yeah.
我想了很多
Been doing a lot of thinking.
然后想象到以后的整个人生  所以...
My life just flashed before my eyes, so...
好吧  我女儿是上帝对我最大的恩赐
Yeah, well, my daughter's my greatest blessing.
温迪看样子会成为一个好妈妈  但是
Now Wendy seems like she'd make a great mom, but--
没错  没错
Yeah. Yeah.
如果你的婚姻并不成功  就别管了
If your marriage doesn't work out, so be it.
但是
But...
你的孩子  他们是你一生的财富
Your kids, they last a lifetime.
本·科森 1999-2007
它在家外
And it knocked down
三个街道处被制伏  无人受伤
three blocks around the house, but no one was hurt.
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
-原来在你那儿啊  -没错
- So that's where it went. - Yeah.
我...
I, uh...
我撞到了你的桌子
I bumped into your desk,
然后这个东西不小心掉到我口袋里了
and it accidentally fell into my pocket.
发现的时候我已经到停车场了
And then by the time I got to the parking lot,
我没有时间...
I didn't have time to...
再回办公室  所以
to come back in, so...
我就亲自来了
Here I am.
这应该是男人想进我家门
This might be one of the worst excuses a guy has ever used
用的最烂的借口了
to try to get into my apartment.
我还以为你会说声谢谢呢
Here I was expecting a thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我明早一大早就得去上班
I have to work so early in the morning.
是的  是的  当然
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
回见
I'll see you around.
好的
Okay.
但你大老远的跑来...
But, I mean, you did come all this way and...
-没错  -所以我们再来一次吧
- Yeah. - So maybe just...one more.
该死
Oh, damn.
晚安
Good night.
快走吧
Go.